a bunch of police with flashing lights and a bunch of bromine on
куча милиции с мигалками и куча броме на
cars some military minister is
машин какой-то министр военный к нам
coming to visit us there is a total ambush I just
приезжает там вообще засада я сейчас
sent a taxi to buy myself some wine
выслала такси чтобы себе купить вина
in short I went to the store even though it is
короче поехала в магазин даже хотя мне
15 meters to the store on foot
до магазина метров 15 пешком
oh I think what is there behind there is
о я думаю что там за там же
[ __ ] where in front of Russia Russia is a blue
[__] где перед Россией россия голубая
country and a bunch of Ukraine I think what is
страна и куча Украина я думаю что же
behind you I immediately understood that this is how it was
зади вас сразу поняла что так оно и было
let's be normal
давайте нормально
look I am from Rostov I am hanging a flag to
смотри я из Ростова я флаг вешаю чтобы
troll Ukrainians relax relax I am one of them
троллить украинцев расслаб расслабься я
yes I understand this is the flag I go under VPN
свой да я понимаю вот это флаг я под VPN
I am trolling Ukrainians I am pretending to be
захожу я украинцев троллю я притворяюсь
theirs I am hanging a yellow and blue flag this one
ихним я вешаю флаг жёлтый с синим этот
that I am sitting on the beach and I start
что я на пляже сижу да с ними начинаю
talking to them they stand there like happy
говорить они стоют такие типа довольные
and then I shout: "And that's it I am from Rostov where are
а потом я кричу: "А и всё я из Ростова
you from where am I from Primorsky Krai the
ты откуда откуда я с Приморского края
city of Usyriysk damn I was in Usyriysk and I was
город Усырийск блин я был в Усырийске и
in Vladivostok can you imagine I was
во Владивостоке был ты представляешь я
driving here  from work now I'll interrupt you for
вот ехала с работы сейчас тебя перебью
a second the day before yesterday I was driving and I look
извини одну секунду позавчера еду смотрю
I live near the railway station that is well my railway is
я около ЖД вокзала живу то есть ну у
right next to it oops it's closed I
меня ЖД прямо вот рядом опа перекрыто
think they closed it the last time they
думаю что перекрыли последний раз
closed it when the Chinese president I
перекрывали когда китайский президент я
was traveling well that's on the
ехала ну по это по
train here they closed it again something
поезду тут опять перекрыли что-то
happened the
случилось
second time I'm driving already the police are standing still I'm
второй раз еду уже вообще милиция стоит
going for the third time there's a bunch of
всё я третий раз иду еду вообще куча
police with flashing lights and a bunch of bromine on
милиции с мигалками и куча броме на
cars some military minister is coming to us
машин какой-то министр военный к нам
there's a total ambush I just
приезжает там вообще засада я сейчас
sent a taxi to buy myself some wine
выслала такси чтобы себе купить вина
in short I went to the store even though it's
короче поехала в магазин даже хотя мне
15 meters to the store on foot well that's how to
до магазина метров 15 пешком ну вот так
go through them I was afraid I thought there were
вот через них идти я побоялась думаю там
equipment and we also have it in Rostov in short
техники а у нас тоже в Ростове короче
when do you remember when Prigozhin was
вот когда это помнишь когда Пригожин на
going to Rostov they also say yes there well with us well it doesn't
Ростов шёл тоже говорят да там ну у нас
fly it it did fly now
ну не долетает было долетало сейчас
Belgorod is very Rostov so far they don't touch
Белгород сильно ростов пока не трогают
Belgorod at all poor I feel so
белгород вообще бедный вообще мне так
sorry why don't they put it there from that
жалко почему туда не поставят из того
place how humanely that's real
места как по-человечески вот реально вот
agree I also have  look at us, people
согласись я тоже у нас смотри у нас люди
don't understand why Putin took it upon himself to protect
не понимают почему Путин взялся защитить
Donbass, he can't protect Belgo, but yes,
Донбасс не может защитить Белго а да вот
I do too, my husband and I discussed the same question
я тоже вот тот же вопрос мы с мужем
the day before yesterday,
обсуждали позавчера
why, why am I collecting money, we need to
почему а почему собираю деньги надо с
take the child from Belgorod to
Белгорода отвестить отвезти ребёнка в
Krasnodar on a real resuscitation
Краснодар на реал реанимационном
plane, why can't Putin take him,
самолёте почему не может Путин отвести
why is it so difficult to call a revolutionary
что это так сложно вызвать революционный
plane to take the child from Belgorod to
самолёт ребёнка отвезти с Белгорода в
Krasnodar, my husband and I are talking about Putin, he
Краснодар вот мы с мужем про Путин себе
wanted to fly cranes, he saw him off
захотел полетал журавлей там он провожал
on a plane, there is money for this, but in order to
на самолёте на это деньги есть а чтобы
transfer the child, we also
ребёнка перевести вот у нас тоже в
brought a girl from Belgorod to Rostov, they took her for 3 days, they took her for
Ростов привозили девочку с Белгорода её
3 days, they stopped
3 дня везли 3 дня везли останавливались
in Voronezh, they pumped her out there, they
в Воронеже они её там откачивали что-то
took her for 3 days, they took her to our Rostov hospital,
3 дня везли в нашу больницу Ростовскую
this is not necessary, let's talk about children, I then
это не надо давай про детей я потом так
worry so much about
переживаю за
this, we don't have our own children, it
это вообще вот своих детей нету
just turns out that people
просто получается у нас тоже как бы люди
are asking us, these bears, all their
спрашивают вот эти медведи у них все
children, in short, have property abroad, they
дети короче за границами имеют имущество
studied abroad, yes, they are warm in
за границами учились да они в тепле в
Moscow  they are sitting and our Belgorod children,
Москве сидят а белгородские дети наши
Rostov children, Krasnodar children should
ростовские краснодарские должны
specifically I was talking to my sister today,
конкретно я с сестрой сегодня
she said that schools are not even
разговаривала она говорит школы даже не
guarded, they are guarded, they say that they guard the
охраняютни охраняют они говорит охраняют
White House, imagine, near the White House, they
белый дом прикинь около белого дома
say all the cars, everything, but you know what's
говорит все машины Всё но знаешь что
most interesting, I also have, uh, my
самое интересное вот у меня тоже у меня
cousin lives in Belgorod, I
ээ двоюродный в Белгороде живёт я ему
tell him: "Go out there to the square near the
говорю: "Выйдите там ну на площадь к
White House and say: "What are you saying,
Белому дому и скажите: "Вы что типа
let's protect us too, what are you only
давайте нас тоже защищайте что вы только
protecting?"  He says: "They'll grab us there
защищаете?" Он говорит: "Там нас
" in short, guys, even my husband,
загребут" короче пацаны даже мой муж
if he says: "We need to defend Belgorod, he'll
если скажет: "Белгород надо защищать он
go" I
пойдёт" вот я тебе
answer you: "Everyone will go" well, the boys will get
отвечаю: "Все пойдут" ну мальчишки
together and go put on a uniform to defend
соберутся и пойдут оденут форму защищать
Belgorod, so Belgorod already needs to be
Белгород так Белгород уже надо идти
defended,
защищать
well, why are the residents there right
ну да там жители почему вот вот вот
now, and they tell me: "Who did you
сейчас а мне говорят: "Ты за кого
vote for?"  Yes of course I voted for
голосовала?" Да конечно я голосовала за
Putin because he started everything and who to
Путина потому что он всё начал а за кого
vote for on the list look who to
голосовать в списке посмотрите за кого
vote for there was no such thing Furgal he was
голосовать нет такого был Фургала его
imprisoned well
посадили
I would have gone for Furgal all the time Purgal there is
ну вот я бы пошла за Фургала всё пургала
no one to vote for well who Zhirinovsky
нету за кого голосовать ну у кого жирик
died if Wait and who imprisoned
умер если Подожди а кто посадил
Purgalova in your place I would not know in your place I would not know
Пургалову у вас бы я не в курсе у вас бы
well Vrgalova I don’t even know I won’t
ну вргалова я даже не знаю я не буду
say well it turns out well Putin
говорить ну это получается ну Путин
imprisoned Furgal and you voted for Putin
посадил Фургала и ты за Путина
yes yes yes I don’t even know
проголосовала да да да я вообще не знаю
who imprisoned him and how Putin has power Putin well
кто его посадил и как путин власть путин
and who I don’t know who did it you
ну а кто я не знаю кто это сделал там
understand it’s their own system well how would it be well it
понимаешь это своя система ну как бы ну
just turns out you wanted to vote
просто получается ты хотела голосовать
for Furgal Putin took and imprisoned Furgal
бы за Фургала Путин взял посадил Фургала
and you voted for Putin it turns out there would have been
а ты проголосовала за Путина получается
No you misunderstood there would have been
был бы Нет ты неправильно понял были бы
fair elections that’s how you
честные выборы вот так
say it would have been Putin Furgal and Zyrik those are the
скажите был бы Путин Фургала и Зырик вот
three yes for
трое да
example Naucha I always voted for Zhirinovsky
например науча я всегда за Жириновского
always that’s how many times I went I
голосовала всегда вот сколько я ходила я
went for  I had no doubts about Zhirinovsky
ходила за не сомневался за Жириновского
Zhirinovsky would not have and if I had
жириновского у бы нету а ещё бы
added a fourth Wagder then I would have
четвёртого добавила Вагдера вот тогда бы
Well listen well look
у меня уже бы Ну слушай ну вот смотри
Putin is already old so if he is now
Путин уже старенький так если он сейчас
like until May 4 for example for whom to
типа до 4 мая например за кого потом
vote then vote and for no one you will
голосовать потом голосовать а не за кого
believe no for no one simply no
вот поверишь нет не за кого просто нет
that Russia will fall apart because there will be no
что Россия развалится бо не будет
president president well honestly I will
президента президента ну вот честно я
tell you there is simply no one to
тебе скажу вот просто не за кого за кого
vote for no one that is it turns out that
голосовать некого то есть получается до
Putin dies before May 4 and that's it and our country will
4 мая умирает Путин и всё и у нас страна
fall apart there will be no president
развалится не будет президента
president well why if there is
президента ну почему если найдётся
such a good
Ванька такой хороший
guy Vanka will stand up well for example any Vanka
мужик встанет ну например какой Ванька
yes any Vanka from the people will stand up and
да любой Ванька из народа встанет
say: "Vote for me" I am such a
скажет: "Голосуйте за меня" я такой
normal guy and people will believe him and he
нормальный пацан и ему поверят люди и он
will show himself that he is a normal guy
покажет себя что он нормальный пацан
why not vote for him there is you
почему бы за него не проголосовать есть
know there is when the country is like
же знаешь есть же когда страна есть
this damn I say why don't they
такая вот блин я говорю почему нас не
lead us there is like this
ведут вот есть такая
when people contribute e we need to
когда люди вносят е вот надо у нас так
do it like this like like if
сделать
I were
как как как вот если б я была
president yes let's say let's
президентом да допустим
say I did it I would for example here are five
допустим я делала я бы например вот пять
candidates yes who are running for
кандидатов да которые идут в
president I would add two lines one
президенты я добавила две строчки одну
line I would add not for anyone that is not for
строчку я бы добавила не за кого то есть
anyone to vote for at all well that
не за не за кого голосовать вообще ну то
is my vote is not
есть мой избирательский голос ни за кого
given to anyone yes and I would add the second line for
не отдаётся да а вторую бы строчку я бы
you to choose well who would you
добавила на выбор вам ну кого бы вы
advise write the last name that is well by
посоветовали напишите фамилию то есть ну
computer election like this well that's
компьютерным избранием вот так ну вот
my personal opinion a very interesting
моё личное мнение очень интересная
electoral system yes I think that the
избирательная система да я думаю что в
Central Electoral Commission and the State Duma would agree
Центр избирком и в Госдуме согласились
that such innovations need to be made
бы что нужно такие нововведения сделать
innovation to make well like this yes then they would
нововедение сделать ну вот так да потом
choose well that's what that's how it happens
выбрали бы ну вот что вот так да бывает
listen but look I can't
слушай а вот смотри я одно не могу
understand one thing with us with you from this Surisk
понять у нас у вас с этого у Суриска
also mobilization took the boys yes like
тоже мобилизацию забрали пацанов да типа
to the front
на фронт
of course but I just didn't with us in Rostov there were
конечно но просто я не у нас в Ростове
so many military they receive a
столько было военных они получают
salary contract soldiers and they took my
зарплату контрактники а забрали у меня
friend they took the boys little boys I have
друга вон забрали пацанов мелких пацани
two and with whom I grew up Sashka
у меня двое а с кем я вросла сашка
Zhenya Zhenya went through Chechnya  went through
Женька женька прошёл и Чечню прошёл
Syria they killed him his second brother they
Сирию его убили второй его брат его
killed my neighbor here he
убили сосед мой вот подстрелянный
came shot already here he is specifically
пришёл уже вот он конкретно
mobilized specifically well
мобилизованный конкретно ну
shot now he is a veteran of military
подстрелянный сейчас он ветеран военных
operations they have already given him a contract and where he was
действий уже ему дали коры а куда ему
shot where somewhere in the leg
подстрелили кудали куда в ногу
like somewhere well in the thigh or down the
типа где-то ну в бедро или вниз ногу
leg down closer to the minister now here he is the
ногу вниз ближе к министку сейчас вот он
hospital will arrive and will return again there they did
госпиталь приедет и вернётся опять туда
not finish shooting it turns out he was shot it turns out
не дострелили получается его далили
him yes yes you listen it
получается его да да ты слушай мне
seems to me that you are not from Belgorod and you
кажется что ты не с Белгород и ты
still hung this flag you as a
всё-таки этот флаг повешал ты как
traitor
предатель
you fell for it
ты повелась
[laughter]
[смех]
give it like yours in short friend neighbor
дари как и твои эти короче дружок сосед
and bro all
и братан все
there
там
[laughter]
[смех]
all divorced I recorded how you
все развёл я записал как ты на Путина
said bad things about Putin that he put Furgal in jail and
говорила плохое что он фургала посадил а
you would have voted for Furgal
ты бы за Фургала голосовала
you said you said you said that
говорила ты говорила ты сказала что
Putin No, he can't that they
Путин Да не может что они защищают
only protect the White House you said that the authorities
только Белый дом ты сказала что власти
protect the White House only I recorded it I recorded
защищают Белый дом только я это записал
I specifically pretend to be
я записал я специально притворяюсь
Russians to us yes I am recording
россиянамни нам да записываю
[laughter]
[смех]
ran away hello
убежал здравствуйте
hello something  I'm not
здравствуйте что-то мне сегодня не
lucky today, everyone switches or wheezes,
фартит вот все переключаются или хрипит
but you came across me and it's nice and the sound is
а вот вы попались и симпатично и звук
good,
хороший
yes, I'm the first, you're the first interlocutor with whom I do
да я первый вы первый собеседник с кем я
n't hear an echo, I've had this before, somehow, I have
эхо не слышу у меня до этого как-то вот
exactly the same
у меня-то точно та такая же
situation, I'm from the city of Kyiv, where am I from, from Moscow, did you
ситуация я из города Киева откуда я из
come to Moscow or were you born
Москвы приехали в Москву или родились
there, was born in Moscow, and how do you communicate, in
там родиглась в Москве а чем общаетесь
general, I practice foreign
вообще тренирую иностранные
languages, but today, for some reason, I'm not in the resource for
языки но сегодня что-то не в ресурс на
foreign languages, what foreign
иностранные языки какие иностранные
languages ​​do you practice, English,
языки вы вообще тренируете английский
Lithuanian, and I studied the
литовский а долгое время изучала
Lithuanian language for a long time and so I decided to
литовский язык и вот решила его
support it because I felt
поддерживать потому что почувствовала
that it was starting, of course, to weaken, I
что он начинает конечно ну ослабевать
tried the French language, but that's all, and
французский язык пыталась но это
why did you learn Lithuanian,
какой-то уже всё а литовский почему
oh, you know, it's linguistically very
ой знаете он лингвистически очень
interesting, firstly, I have roots, and
интересно у меня во-первых корни есть а
secondly, the language is quite close to Sanskrit, yes, yes,
во-вторых язык а довольно к санскриту
yes, there are even words for "virus,"
близкий да дадада там даже слова вирус
here's a man, and in Lithuanian
вот мужчина а в литовском
Sanskrit, of course, the
санскрите и такой конечно
language is lacy, that's what you can say about the language,
язык кружевной вот можно так про язык
it's intricate,
сказать он затейливый
I generally really like such complex languages
я вообще очень люблю такие сложные языки
that  preserved archaic
которые сохранили архаичные
traces English of course well it does not
следы английский конечно ну он не это не
spoil with this well there are people who are
балует этим ну есть люди которые там
starting to learn ancient Chinese that is
начинают древнекитайский учить то есть
they somehow but they go to such languages
они как-то а вот в такие языки уходят
that have already kind of
которые уже как бы
lost well they have already changed a lot
утратили ну они уже сильно изменились аа
but Lithuanian it is of course amazing in that it has
вот литовский он конечно поразителен тем
practically not changed over such
что он практически не изменился за такие
long centuries these here period is
долгие там столетия вот эти вот период
huge
огромный
eh it is amazing
э это удивительно
you were talking so excitedly about the Lithuanian language
вы так возбуждённо про литовский язык
not this is mine this is mine just
рассказывали не это моя это моё просто
simply this is mine and what are your roots
просто это моё а какие у вас корни
Lithuanian and on my father's side my
литовские а по отцу у меня
grandfather was from somewhere in Lithuania and
дед откуда-то из Литвы был а остальные
where are the rest of the roots and
корни откуда
Russian
а русские
Polish maybe Jewish there are I don't know
польские может еврейские есть не знаю
Russians where
русские откуда
in the sense of Russians well from which provincial
в смысле русские ну с каких губерниских
regions
областей
and something Smolensk is this is not this
а что-то Смоленское есть это не это
Belarusians well
белорусы
yes there is such a contiguity and and Moscow I
ну да там такая смежность а и Москва
understand and
понял
you I am a Jew
а у вас я еврей
and you know Hebrew no and I tried to learn I didn't
а вы знаете иврит нет а я пыталась учить
succeed
у меня ничего не получилось
I have a similar situation I thought then I
у меня схожая ситуация я подумала потом
think: "No better"
думаю: "Нет лучше"
I know Hebrew it is a very
я знаете иврит он очень для начинающих
impolite language for beginners because  vowels these and
невежливый язык потому что огласовки вот
if you don't know these vowels
эти вот а если этих огласов не не знаешь
yes yes
да да
you're
ты
just well intolerant language you can't
просто ну нетолерантный язык ты не
read a word if you don't
можешь слово прочитать если ты его не
know it can you like this well how would you like m
знаешь можно можно вам такое ну как бы м
this how to say it softly so that uh an
это как правильно сказать мягко чтобы ээ
intimate linguistic question to ask
интимный лингвистический вопрос задать
it I don't know if I can answer I've
его я не знаю смогу ли я ответить я мне
never been asked
никогда не задавали
intimate linguistic questions question
интимно-лингвистических вопросов вопрос
yes whose Crimea is it not this is
да чей Крым
not a linguistic question it's a
это не это не лингвистический вопрос это
political question
политический вопрос
linguistic whose Crimea
лингвистический чей Крым
is a political question I'm not talking
это политический вопрос я не говорю
about politics here
здесь про политику
whose Crimea
чей Крым
Crimea Crimean I don't know what to answer you
крым крымский не знаю что вам ответить
Crimea Crimean well what am I and why are you
крым крымский да ну что я а почему ты
like
такая
oh listen you're switching to insults
ой слушайте вы переходите на оскорбление
yes because Crimea is Crimean and not
да потому что Крым крымский а не
Ukrainian because you will support the
украинский потому что ты поддержишь
murder of people in my country because
убийство людей в моей стране потому что
you are responsible for this
ты ответственная за эту
war andro doesn't know how to break
войну андро не умеет обломать
hello Ukraine let's talk normally
здравствуте Украина давайте нормально
let's say hello Ukraine I'm
давайте я говорю здравствуйте Украина я
from the city of Khmelnitsky Ukraine and where are you from
из города Хмельниц Украина а вы откуда
we are from Severouralsk we have Ukrainian
мы с Североуральска у нас украинские
surnames mine Dudchenko is Bagma
фамилии у меня Дудченко это Багма
cool and what are you talking about here and we are
прикольно а чём общаетесь тут а мы сидим
just sitting and relaxing together with a friend you
просто отдыхаем вдвоём с подругой лаваш
are eating lavash
едите
m lavash you are eating
м лаваш едите
sausage
колбаса
husbands are at war now
мужья сейчас на войне
no on duty in the forest got it logging workers yeah got it what do you
нет на вахте в лесу понял лесоповальщики
think why is this
понял как вы вообще считаете почему эта
war going on
война идёт
I don't understand why this
я вообще не понимаю зачем это вообще
war happened at all why what for what what are they dividing who is being divided who is being divided
война случилась зачем для чего что делят
I don't understand if
кого делят кого делят я не понимаю если
Putin is already friends with Trump then what he won't take
Путин с Трампом уже дружит то что он не
troops from Ukraine
заберёт войска из Украины
I don't understand at all either well if everyone has already
я вообще не понимаю тоже ну если всё уже
become friends with America
с Америкой подружились можно убегать
we can run away we should run away Russia or Ukraine
мы должны убегать россия или Украина
in general Russia Ukraine look Russia
вообще россия украина смотри Россия
attacked Ukraine so that America wouldn't
напала на Украину чтобы Америка типа не
set up its bases if Russia has already
поставила свои базы если Россия уже
made friends with Trump America isn't
подружилась с Трампом Америка базы не
setting up bases then Russia can leave
ставит то Россия может уходить из
Ukraine really well
Украины правда
probably it turns out that way I
ну наверное получается так
understood why it isn't taking what Putin doesn't
понял а что она не забирает что Путин не
want peace
хочет мира
apparently no apparently they are dividing something else it
видимо нет видимо ещё что-то делят
turns out that
получается
Zelensky is probably being divided
так Зеленского наверное делят
and Putin wants to capture Zelensky in short well well
а Путин хочет короче захватить
apparently that's what I think
Зеленского да ну видимо так я думаю
Ukraine and Russia they used to be
Украина и Россия они раньше вообще
friends why the war  started why not not
друзья были почему война началась почему
friends girlfriends
не не друзья подруги
well girlfriends girlfriends yes that's how you
ну подруги подруги да вот как вы
yeah
угу
one is normal another Russia is one and
одна нормальная другая Россия одна а
one is normal - this is Ukraine yes although we
одна нормальная - это Украина да хотя мы
ourselves also
сами тоже
and you understand we live in Russia that's how to
и понимаешь в России живём вот как это
understand this well now you have already become Russified
понимать ну вот вы стали уже обрусевшие
mankurts yes
манкурты да
so you already know us and they pull here and there and we do
так нас уже знаешь и туда и сюда тянут и
n't
не
understand the war will end you are already Russian
понимаем война закончится вы уже русские
you are already Russian
вы уже русские
well what to do in this situation I see
ну что делать в этой ситуации я смотрю у
you have an icon of Christ the Savior yes yes yeah
вас икона Христа Спасителя да есть да
yeah everyone Orthodox
угу всё православные
yes we are Orthodox we I
да мы православные мы я я семинарию
graduated from seminary I have spiritual orders I am a
заканчивал у меня есть духовный сан я
priest it's nice to hear yes even
священник это приятно слышать да даже 3
served in the church for 3 years
года служил в церкви
then went well like a priest yes or Yes yes
потом пошёл ну типа батюшка да или Да да
priest yeah yeah by the way
батюшка
you know the symbol of faith I do
угу вы кстати символ веры
n't know no we don't know and Our Father
знаете не знаю нет мы не знаем а отче
about Our Father yes well how do you say Our Father in Russia
о Отче наш да а ну как у вас в России
anu tell me well that's how well
Отче наш говорят ану скажите
I'm just like that
ну вот так вот ну я вот так вот просто
usually well a prayer there like Our Father and
вот обычно ну молитву там как Отче наш и
live si sii nebesi as you say well
жи си небеси как у вас говорят а ну
tell me I want to listen
скажите я хочу послушать
but I don't know I just  I say: "Lord,
а я не знаю я просто говорю: "Господи
I thank you that I'm alive" that's how I
благодарю тебя за то что я жива" вот так
pray and you know Our Father
вот я молюсь а вы знаете Отче наш
Our Father I know yes say live in
отче наш я знаю да скажите живе на
heaven there and hallowed be thy name and
небеси там и да святится имя твоё и
thy kingdom come and
пребудет царствие твоё да и пребудет
thy will be done and forever and ever and ever
твоя воля и во веки истину и во веки
amen there well well that's something like that
веков аминь там вот ну вот что-то вот
somehow I know that's how I understood
так вот как-то я вот так вот знаю понял
not you have some kind of abbreviated prayer maybe you
не у вас какая-то урезанная молитва
know normally no I didn't
может вы нормально знаете нет я не до
finish it maybe I just finished reading it let's say maybe I'm like
конца её может просто дочитала вот
Our Father and
допустим может я как бы отче наш и же
if uh I'm in heaven let thy name shine
если ээ я на небеси да светится имя твоё
let thy kingdom come let thy will be done so I Come on let's let's let's let's help now I'll say you'll repeat now let's pray a normal
да придёт царствие твоё да будет воля
prayer full come on let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's let's say you're going to repeat now let's pray a normal prayer full come on let's ...
молитвы полной давайте давайте давайте
thy kingdom thy will be done
да пребудет царствие твоё да будет воля
thy will be done so that
да будет воля твоя чтоб
[laughter]
[смех]
Putin simply divorced us
Путин нас вообще просто развёл
not with you
не с тобой
thy will be done so that Zelensky
да будет воля твоя чтобы Зеленский
and everything God is with us and not with you ha-ha-ha
а всё Бог с нами а не с вами ха-ха-ха
all of you Yes come on come on yes
всё вы Да давай
it was a bomb like subscribe comment it's a
это была бомба лайк подписка коммент
pity I didn't see them no I closed my eyes
жалко я не видел их не Я закрывал глаза
I'll watch the recording later
я потом посмотрю запись
Shabbat shalom oops
шаббат шалом ёпта
oh it's cool with you inshallah
о прикольно у тебя иншаллах
inshabbatashala it's
иншабаташала
cool in short how much does it cost per hour an hour
прикольно короче сколько стоит в час час
what does it cost cool how much does it cost
что стоит прикольная сколько в час стоит
per hour what cool how much does it charge per hour
прикольная сколько в час берёт
inshabahalaha how much do you cost
иншабахалаха сколько стоишь
I didn't understand at all what I understood and which one did
я вообще не понял то что я понял а какая
n't well like this redhead how much does she
нет ну типа вот эта рыжеволосая сколько
charge per hour
в час берёт
usually a thousand
обычно тыся
rubles maybe 10 and how much does it cost with you
рублей может быть 10 а у вас сколько
wait are you really for an hour or are you for a
подожди а ты реально на час или ты на
day what kind of
день какое мусульманство вообще
Islam do you know that now is
мусульманство знаете что сейчас идёт
harab do you know what harak is the
хараб вы знаете что такое харак
holy month of Ramadan the holy month of
священный месяц Рамадан священный месяц
Ramadan is called Muslims you seem to have
Рамадан называется мусульман у вас
holy month of Ramadan today
походу священный месяц Драмадан сегодня
you have Ramadan holy month neither meat
у вас Рамадан священный месяц ни мясо не
nor dairy products nor eggs at all they
едят ни молочные продукты ни яйца вообще
eat nothing at all income with nothing at all got it
ничего не едят вообще дохода со вообще
super and what do you have to do with
ничего понял супер а ты причём к
Ramadan nothing can be eaten you can't
Рамадану ничего есть нельзя
drink milk you can't eat eggs you
нельзя молоко пить нельзя яйца есть
can't eat nasty stuff you can't with us Muslims
нельзя бяку нельзя у нас у мусульман
such haram goes that is
такой харам идёт
you this not now we are a
то есть тебя этот не сейчас у нас
Muslim country we can't do this what is
мусульманская страна у нас нельзя такого
your country a Muslim
какая у вас страна страна мусульманская
country the republic of Tatarstan the city of Kazan the
страна республика Татарстан город Казань
city of Kazan is a Muslim country the
город Казань- мусульманская страна
republic of Tatarstan oh and you are a Muslim
республика Татарстан о и ты мусульманка
now in short in Ramadan in the month of Ramadan
сейчас короче в Драмадан в месяц Рамадан
yes exactly what exactly yes exactly yes that's
да именно что именно да именно
why we came out here and clean out
да мы поэтому вышли сюда и прочистить
people like you and and you are Russian who
таких людей как вы а а ты русская кто
will be rude to whom who can lie who doesn't
кому будет хамить кто может врёт кто не
lie listen and your hairy friend what
врёт слушай а твой волосатый друг кто по
nationality is this you ca
национальности
n't do this you can't be rude you can't be rude you can't be rude too haram haram to be rude you ca
так нельзя так нельзя нельзя харм нельзя
n't communicate honestly boor you
харам хамить нельзя общаться честно
can't smoke at all you
хамик нельзя вообще курю вообще хомить
can't be rude at all and to wear clothes listen man why is a
нельзя а одевать одежду слушай мужик что
woman interrupting you she doesn't
тебя женщина перебивает ты она тебя не
respect you if she interrupts you  oh
уважает если она тебя перебивает а ну
come on if you are a man then come on talk to
давай если ты мужчина то давай говори со
me like a man in the morning yes why is a
мной как мужчина утра да что тебя
woman interrupting you you really I don't
женщина перебивает ты реально Я тебя не
respect you because your woman doesn't
уважаю потому что тебя твоя женщина не
respect you she interrupts you if you
уважает она тебя перебивает если ты не
can't shut the mouth of a girl who
можешь закрыть рот девушки которая
interrupts you then you are worthless as a
перебивает тебя тогда грош тебе цена как
man the first discovery
мужчина первым открытием
you see you are not a man you can't
ты видишь ты не мужик ты не можешь
calm down who interrupts you you can't drink
успокоить которая перебивает тебя пить
not to mention eat you can't drink and you
нельзя не то чтобы есть нельзя пить и
can't shout at all to say any
нельзя вообще кричать говорить какие-то
thoughts okay what is your name Snow White you
мысли хорошо как тебя зовут Белоснежка
can't pray even from 4 am to 4 am you ca
молиться нельзя даже вот с 4 утра до 4
n't at all this ha this is nonsense
утра вообще нельзя это ха это забред
Islam everything I live in a Muslim
мусульманство всё я живу в мусульманской
country
стране
for us it is haram a man such a bridge he doesn't give a [ __ ]
для нас это харам мужчина такой мост
I'm in
вообще ему срет я в
Tatarstan oh my
Татарстане
god everything is forbidden you can't but you can drink
боже тере всё нельзя тебе нельзя а а
in Ramadan it is haram for us now haram
бухать можно в Рамадан у нас сейчас
and drinking is haram
харам харам а бухать - это харам
Muslims haram Tatarstan the city of Kazan the
мусульмане харам татарстан город Казань
Republic of Tatarstan
Республика Татарстан
yours will be cut off for everyone you can't
вашку всем отрежет нельзя
understand with all due respect little
понимаешь при всём уважении маленьким
boys
мальчикам
are cut and they say: "Mom I wo
режут а они говорят: "Мама у меня больше
n't have anymore" they don't  understand this
не будет" они не понимают это
Muslim extreme flesh yes they circumcise
мусульманску крайнюю плочь да обрезают у
we have a great holiday today we have a fast we have a
нас сегодня великий праздник у нас пост
great fast and not a
идёт у нас великий пост идёт и у нас ни
single man will drink anything until 4 in the morning until 4 in the evening not a single
один мужик до 4 утра до 4 ветри ни один
man will drink anything even water
мужик ничего даже воды не будет пить о
what are you talking about we have a Muslim
чём ты говоришь у нас мусульманская
country the Republic of
страна Республика
Tatarstan I am calling you from the city of Kazan
Татарстан я тебе звоню из города Казань
this is the Republic the capital all our men
это Республика столица у нас все мужики
support us thank God we
поддерживают у нас слава богу мы вот так
can applaud like this we have
вот можно поаплодировать
men take an example from them and
у нас мужики вот с них пример бери а
condemn but you don't have this and do you have at least
осуждать а у вас такого нет а у вас хоть
one such holiday no I wish you
один такой праздник есть нет желаю вам
honestly health and just intelligence really
вот честно здоровья и просто ума правда
be healthy and happy in your own way
будьте здоровы и счастливы вот по-своему
wait what is your name what is your
вот подожди как тебя зовут как тебя
name in
зовут
the east my name is Mahmud very
восточно меня Махмуд зовут очень
nice your name is Regina is it
приятное у тебя имя регина
wrong something wanted to get in the way
это непра что-то хотели подлезаться
probably yes no no Regina I want to
наверное да нет нет регина я хочу
ask but how is it in Tatarstan
спросить а вот как у вас в Татарстане
in the month of Ramadan can you drink
вот в месяц Рамадан можно ли пить
alcohol wait wait wait wait
алкоголь подожди подожди подожди подожди
why couldn't you initially talk to me
а почему изначально ты не мог со мной ну
like normally I
как бы по-нормальному поговорить я тебя
what to you  nahomila nagrutila and Mahmud from what
что нахомила нагрутила а Махмуд с какой
country is his name well, especially today I
страны имя ну вот тем более сегодня я
communicate with people who are of a different
общаюсь с людьми которые другой
nationality this is also not And what
национальности это тоже не А какой он
nationality is he today you communicate with
национальности сегодня ты общаешься с
him what nationality is he why in
ним какой он национальности почему в
the end here can I ask you a question
итоге вот можно вопрос вам задать
can I ask a question like a human being
можно вопрос вот по-человечке задать
look I'm not uh not a
посмотрите я не ээ не
nationalist I kind of well with understanding
националист я как бы ну с пониманием
yours to each here is what you are trying to
ваше каждому вот вы что пытаетесь нам
convey to us
донести
here you tell me first
вот вы сначала мне
I will explain to you then and then
скажите я потом вам объясню а потом
maybe we will become friends so Regina
может быть мы подружимся так Регина
look what nationality is your
смотрите какой национальности ваш
current friend initially introduce yourself
сегодняшний друг изначально представься
please my name is Mahmud
пожалуйста меня зовут Махмуд
Mahmud this is a real name real yes yes
махмуд это настоящее имя настоящее да да
my father is from Syria Izri Dani cigarettes
у меня отец из Сирии изри дани сигарет
what nationality is your current friend
какй национальности ваш друг сегодняшний
and why are you interested in my friend well what
а причём почему вас мой друг интересует
nationality is he is silent
ну какая у него национальность молчит
what nationality nationality and
какой национальности национальности а
wait and why are you interested in my friend
подожди а зачем вас мой друг интересует
nationality well you said that you are
национальности ну ты же сказала что ты
with a person of a different nationality today
сегодня с человеком другой
so besides his nationality was
так помимо его национальность было
he Russian you don't have Russian
он русский у тебя
at all not Russian
нет не русский вообще не русский
no we don't no well like Egyptian
нет мы не не ну как бы египетский
and why is he well, I wonder, a man,
а зачем он-то ну интересно мужчина ты
can you answer what nationality are you
можешь ответить кто-то по национальности
afraid of? No, no, I don't think so, I don't
что боишься нет ну нет я не считаю я не
think it's necessary. Look, a woman is shutting you up. You're
считаю нужным смотри тебя женщина
afraid to answer. Your
затыкает ты боишься ответить свою
nationality. A woman is shutting you up. This is a
национальность женщина тебя затыкает это
disgrace in the
позор в месяц Рамадан простом
month of Ramadan. A woman is shutting you
в месяц Рамадан женщина затыкает тебе
up. This is simply my God. If a
рот это просто боже Аллах если это видит
man sees this, this is a disgrace. Okay,
это позор мужчины ладно ты
what am I a witness? You've disgraced your
что я свидетель ты опозорила своего
man. This is yes, you
мужчину этого да ты во время Рамадана
shut him up during Ramadan in front of another man. It's
заткнула ему рот при другом мужчине с
okay to negotiate with you. My name is
тобой нормально договориться меня зовут
Really, really, a man. You're not a man anymore.
Реально реально мужик ты уже не мужик
Allah saw everything and I saw you. Regina
всё Аллах видел и я видел тебя Регина
just threw aside some
просто откинула как знаешь какую-то
rubber. She just pushed it away with her hand. Her last name is
резину просто рукой оттолкнула фамилия
Goltsman
Гольцман
Goltsman. Well, what are you talking about?
гольцман ну тебе это о чём ты говори а
This is cunning Goltsman. I understand you here. I understand.
это хитрый Гольцман тебя тут понял
And what did you change? I just
понял а что ты поменял-то я просто её
can't switch it off. I
переключать не могу никак
understand. Listen, young Goltsman. She's at least
понял слушай а юный Гольцман она вообще
pretty.
хоть хороша
Everything has switched over. This is
всё переключилась вот это
the content we have for a month.
контент у нас месяц
subscribe to my Instagram I don't
дробода підпишись на мій Instagram я не
know why it's for what else you're there to watch
знаю для чго це для чого ще тобі там
but for you it's one two
дивитись на ост але для тебе це один два
or three clicks but you support me and I
або три клика але ти підтримаєш мене и я
'll say: "Wow I have a lot of followers
буду казати: "Вау в мене там купа фолове
and I'll have a great time making new
и в мене буде класний настб робити нові
ones like you Andrey"
крупшись на й попик Андрей"
so let me wait for you
отак давай я тебе очекаю